Trice, Harrison M., Audio-Visual Materials /4164 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Harrison M. Trice Audio-Visual Materials
1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Trice, Harrison M.
/4164 AV
18.33 cubic feet
18.3 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
Mostly audio cassette tapes, may be interviews, speeches, etc.
8455938
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4164: Harrison M. Trice Additional Papers /3010: Harrison Trice Papers /4254: Harrison Trice Additional Books
Trice, Harrison Miller, 1920-
8455938
- Nilson (tape 1) (Box 1)
- Nilson (con't) - Hart, Barnet, Dr. Hansen (tape 2) (Box 2)
- Dr. Hansen (con't) (tape 3) (Box 3)
- Mallmann HMT (tape 4) (Box 4)
- Head Nurse (cont.) HMT (tape 5) (Box 5)
- Head Nurse (cont.) HMT (tape 6) (Box 6)
- Ric &; harry E.A.P. - 8/1979 (tape 7) (Box 7)
- Denver E.A.P. - William Goldenstein, Section Chief/Personnel - (tape 2) (Box 8)
- Ric & Harry - E.A.P. - 8/1979 (tape 7) (Box 9)
- E.A.P. Interview - Dr. Hipp - 8/1/1979 (Box 10)
- J.B.T. Denver E.A.P. - continuation of Bill McGinley (tape 2) (Box 11)
- J.B.T. Denver E.A.P. - continuation Smith/Par - (tape 3) (Box 12)
- J.B.T. Denver E.A.P. - Bill Goldstein Section Chief beginning of Supervisor McGinley (tape 1) (Box 13)
- Denver E.A.P. - Head Nurse (Box 14)
- J.B.T. - Dr. Lewis (beginning) (tape 1) (Box 15)
- J.B.T. - Kansas City - Jack Gross (tape 2) (Box 16)
- J.B.T. - Ron Atkins (concluded) (tape 3) (Box 17)
- 3rd Level - Sladkey (Box 18)
- Kansas City E.A.P. - Dr. Roberts: 3/1980 (Box 19)
- Kansas City E.A.P. - V.P., C.W.A.: 3/1980 (Box 20)
- Kansas City - E.A.P. - Ron Akeus (Box 21)
- Kansas City - E.A.P. - Dr. Lewis I (Box 22)
- Kansas City - E.A.P. - Tape II (Box 23)
- Denver - E.A.P. - H.M.T. - Larry McGinley (Box 24)
- Denver - E.A.P. - H.M.T. - 12/1979 (Box 25)
- Denver - E.A.P. - J.B.T. - Male Section Chief - tape 1 (Box 26)
- Denver - E.A.P. - Misc. Info. On P.A.R. Assoc.: tape 2 (Box 27)
- Denver - E.A.P. - J.B.T. - Denver - General Manager Dept. Chief - Remarks - PAR Assoc. - tape 1 (Box 28)
- HMT PAR Associates - Denver - 12/1979 (Box 29)
- Denver - H.M.T. - 12/1979 - Palmquart - Comptroller (Box 30)
- Denver - 12/18/1979 - H.M.T. (Box 31)
- Denver - Zargella - HMT - 12/1979: tape 9 (Box 32)
- Atlanta - E.A.P. - tape 1 (Box 33)
- Atlanta - E.A.P. - tape 2 (Box 34)
- Atlanta - E.A.P. - tape 3 (Box 35)
- Atlanta - E.A.P. - tape 4 (Box 36)
- Atlanta - E.A.P. - tape 5 (Box 37)
- Kansas City - E.A.P. - G Mat (Box 38)
- Kansas City - E.A.P. - Tape no. 4: Dr. Reinhardt (Box 39)
- Atlanta - E.A.P.: tape 1 (Box 40)
- Atlanta - E.A.P.: Dr. Beckoff (concluded); Mr. Peterson, Dr. Ballard (beg.); Atlanta Region -- tape 2 (Box 41)
- Denver - HMT - Dr. Zarlengo, Medical Director: tape 1 (Box 42)
- Denver - HMT: Dr. Zarlengo, Medical Director -- tape 2 (Box 43)
- Corp. Headquarters. - AIC Policy, Part of Dr. Beckoff, Atlanta E.A.P.: tape 2 (Box 44)
- Corp. Headquarters. - AIC Policy - Part of Dr. Beckoff - Atlanta E.A.P.: tape 3 (Box 45)
- Corp. Headquarters. - AIC Policy: Part of Dr. Beckoff - Atlanta - E.A.P. -- tape 4 (Box 46)
- Corp. Headquarters. - AIC Policy - Part of Dr. Beckoff - Atlanta E.A.P.: tape 5 (Box 47)
- Corp. Headquarters. - AIC Policy - Part of Dr. Beckoff - Atlanta - E.A.P.: tape 6 (Box 48)
- Corp. Headquarters. - AIC Policy: Al Upshaw -- Atlanta -- Tape 1 (Box 49)
- Corp. Headquarters. - ALC Policy - AL Upshaw: Atlanta - Tape 2 -- Supplement to CCRP Headquarters. Interviews - 8/2/1979 (Box 50)
- Corp. Headquarters. - ALC Policy - Al Upshaw: Atlanta -- 8/1/1979 -- tape 3 (Box 51)
- St. Louis - E.A.P.: tape 1 -- 7/10/1979 (Box 52)
- St. Louis - E.A.P.: tape 2 (Box 53)
- St. Louis - E.A.P.: tape 3 (Box 54)
- Kansas City - E.A.P.: no other labelling (Box 55)
- Kansas City - E.A.P.: Kroupa - Kansas City - HMT - Mar. 1980 (Box 56)
- Kansas City - E.A.P. - Dr. Reinhardt - H.M.T. - Kansas City Works - Mar. 1980 (Box 57)
- Kansas City - E.A.P.: HMT - Mar. 1980 - Mayer & McMillan (Box 58)
- Misc. noes from all over: HMT (Box 59)
- Audit (Box 60)
- Kardeen - Mar. 4: Obs, don't hype; on stenorette to about 50 (half) (Box 61)
- Dan Forget (Box 62)
- Ashley Johnson - completed (Box 63)
- Ric, Harry & Lee Union - 8/1979: (tape 3) (Box 64)
- Ric & harry & Lee Overview of locations - 8/1979: tape 4 (Box 65)
- Ric, Harry & Lee overview of location, discussion of instruments - 8/1979: tape 6 (Box 66)
- Ric, harry & Lee - Overview of locations - 8/1979: tape 5 (Box 67)
- Ric, Harry - Indianapolis, Hawthorne & King of Prussia: 3/1979 -- tape 1 (Box 68)
- C.A.L. discussion Apr. 6 (Box 69)
- Thio Colby (Box 70)
- Round IV FBC: Merrick Glover (Box 71)
- Finn, Koziar-Rosette, Smith, George Jr. Republic, Confidential - 12/16/1976 (Box 72)
- Selden Bacon - 7/20/1976: HMT (Box 73)
- Magruder: FBC; Hy Myers -- THIO (Box 74)
- Roman on OPC's: '76 NCA, 1976 (Box 75)
- Bill Stump & typed 3/5/1976; Don McGruder (Box 76)
- Miriam Guida: FBC; Asley Johnson -- FBC (Box 77)
- Alden Asbornnen - finished: 3/8/1976 (Box 78)
- Thio - Mary Gallagher - 10/15/1975; Dick Magee - 10/16/1975 (Box 79)
- Bill Williams - finished 3/4/1976 (Box 80)
- Round II (Division) Asbornsen, Kapa, Delaney; Round V Bill Christian, Miriam Guida (Box 81)
- Jerry Rooney - Rounds I-IV (Box 82)
- Observation LeSavage Glover, Round I, Mitchell Rooney Atkin (Box 83)
- Bob Smith - Round V - THIO (Box 84)
- Damon - 3/1976 (Box 85)
  Scope and Contents
  begin at mid-tape
- Dictation Date - Oct. 17: Don Kapa (Box 86)
- Karen Zuckerman (Box 87)
- Round I - THIO - Bill Christian / Miriam Guida (Box 88)
- Dan Driscoll - THIO - Round V (Box 89)
- Cliff Fuller - THIO (Box 90)
- Tim Kardeen - THIO - Oct. 8; Bill Hull - THIO - Oct. 9 (Box 91)
- Begin Merrick taped 4 Nov.: THIO--- 12/1/1975 (Box 92)
- Bud Le Salvage: THIO (Box 93)
- Round V: THIO -- Ashley Johnson; Kevin Murray (Box 94)
- Unlabeled (Box 95)
- Bob Maloney (Box 96)
- Jerry Waters, Chief Brant, Reo Perlis (Box 97)
- Round I: Bob Bell, Chief Brant (Box 98)
- Round I - Karen Zuckerman; Alden Asbornsen (Box 99)
- Round I - John Fulton - finished 3/11/1975 (Box 100)
- Bill Gulliver - THIO (Box 101)
- Ric - Atlanta Works - 6/6/1978; Asst. Med. Div. & Plant Tour (Box 102)
- Jack Butter - 1/16/1975 (Box 103)
- Christian/Smith/Fulton/McGee (Box 104)
- Mary Gallagher - FBC (Box 105)
- Round I - Bill Gulliver (Box 106)
- Round I - NCA - Affiliate - Bob Macmillan (Box 107)
- Hull Observation - Kardeen Observation - Colby Observation (Box 108)
- The "Next" tape (Box 109)
- Round I - Stan Glover, Mike Merrick (Box 110)
- Discussion C.A.L.: Apr. 6, 1976 (Box 111)
- Round I - Miriam Guida (Box 112)
- Stan Glover: THIO (Box 113)
- Atlanta - WE-Cable & Wire & Regional Office (Box 114)
- Atlanta (WE) - June, 1978 (JAM) (Box 115)
- Reading goodies - Alice & Cindy: 4/24/1978 (Box 116)
- Harry - 'reaction' to our tapes on visit to WE's Atlanta Works (Box 117)
- Ric - Syracuse Svc. Ctr. (5/11/1978) (Box 118)
- Unlabeled (Box 119)
- N.Y. State Troopers - Delello, Zinn, Zimmerman (Box 120)
- Agricultural & Biological Engineering as a Profession (tape no. 5) (Box 121)
- Ric - Atlanta (6/8/1978) (Box 122)
- WE interview - J. Berger (Box 123)
- Round I - Bob Smith (Box 124)
- Dick McGee, Mary Gallagher, Bob Smith, Stan Glover (Box 125)
- Tom Delaney (Box 126)
- John Quinn (Box 127)
- Cindy - June, 1978 - Atlanta Service Center & Installation (Box 128)
- Atlanta Works (Box 129)
- Ric - July, 1978 (Box 130)
- Jan. - Atlanta (WE) - June 1978 (Box 131)
- W.E. Interviews with Supervisors, nurses & persons dir. Of engineers - 4/25/1978 (Box 132)
- Cindy - Reading - 4/20/1978: Tom Hahn, Dr. Frantz & Betty (Box 133)
- Cindy - WE Atlanta Works - Cable & Wire - June 1978 (Box 134)
- Supervisor Interviews (Box 135)
- RIC - Syracuse Svc. Ctr. (5/11/1978) (Box 136)
- Unlabeled (Box 137)
- Ric - Atlanta (6/7/1978) - Regional Headquarters. (Box 138)
- Ric - Atlanta Regional Headquarters (Box 139)
- Ric - (Box 140)
- Jan - Atlanta Works (June 1978) (Box 141)
- Harry - 'reaction' to our tapes our visit to WE's Atlanta Works (Box 142)
- Cindy - Atlanta Regional Office - Head Nurse - June 1978; Reading Works - Union - June 1978 (Box 143)
- Goodies - Cindy - 3/9/1976 (Box 144)
- Goal Interviews (Box 145)
- Dan Forget (Box 146)
- Finished - Cliff Fuller, Mike Colby (Box 147)
- Unlabeled (Box 148)
- Unlabeled (Box 149)
- Unlabeled (Box 150)
- Unlabeled (Box 151)
- Unlabeled (Box 152)
- 1.3 A, 1 (Box 153)
- 2.3, 2 (Box 153)
- 4.2 A + B, 3 (Box 153)
- 11.1, 11.2, 11.3 A, 4 (Box 153)
- 1.2, 5 (Box 153)
- 10.1, 10.2, 10.3, 6 (Box 153)
- 1.1 A + B [#1], 7 (Box 153)
- 1.1 C [#2], 8 (Box 153)
- 2.1 A, 2.2 A, 9 (Box 153)
- 5.3 B, 6.1, 6.2 A, 10 (Box 153)
- 2.2 B, 2.3 A, 11 (Box 153)
- 7.1, 7.2, 7.3, 12 (Box 153)
- 7.4, 9.4, 10.4, 11.4, 13 (Box 153)
- Final, 14 (Box 153)
- 4.3 B, 5.1, 15 (Box 153)
- 5.4, 6.4, 16 (Box 153)
- 3.1, 3.2, 3.3, 4.1, 17 (Box 153)
- 12.1, 12.2, 13.3, 12.3, 18 (Box 153)
- B. Challenger; Colby - March 1976, 19 (Box 153)
- Bob Smith - I, 20 (Box 153)
- Bob Smith II, 21 (Box 153)
- Unlabeled, 22 (Box 153)
- Nassau County Drug, 23 (Box 153)
- Unlabeled, 24 (Box 153)
- History: Bill Staudenmeir (pulled from /4164 - box 64 ff42) (Box 154)
- History: Bill Staudenmeir (pulled from /4164 - box 64 ff42) (Box 155)
- History of AA by HMT - 6/24/1987 (pulled from /4164 - box 64 ff43) (Box 156)
- History of AA by HMT - 6/24/1987 (pulled from /4164 - box 64 ff43) (Box 157)